Millard Powers Fillmore Legal Papers
State University of New York at Oswego
Millard Powers Fillmore Legal Papers
1830 - 1890
The legal papers consist of court records, reports, and notes on the numerous cases which Powers Fillmore litigated between 1869 and the middle 1880’s. The legal records include documents relevant to the proceedings of the circuit, county, district, and State Supreme Courts of New York State. Earlier documented cases from the 1830’s and 1850’s are present within the collection.
2 boxes
Fillmore, Millard Powers, 1828-1889
State University of New York at Oswego Penfield Library 7060 State Route 104 Oswego, New York 13126-3599
2011.023.0001
Collection is open to the public.
Millard Powers Fillmore was the son of Millard Fillmore, the 13th President of the United States, and his first wife Abigail Powers. Powers Fillmore was a well respected citizen and prominent lawyer in the region of Erie County and Buffalo, New York.
Fillmore, Millard Powers, 1828-1889; Fillmore, Darius Ingraham, 1814-1837; Lawyers--New York (State)--Erie County; Lawyers--New York (State)--Buffalo; Fillmore, Caroline Carmichael; Lawyers
The legal papers consist of court records, reports, and notes on the numerous cases which Powers Fillmore litigated between 1869 and the middle 1880’s. The legal records include documents relevant to the proceedings of the circuit, county, district, and State Supreme Courts of New York State. Earlier documented cases from the 1830’s and 1850’s are present within the collection. The financial records and copies of family correspondence, to a minor extent, are also contained in the collection.
- Accounts, 1868 - 1875 (Box-folder 01-01)
  Accounts
  - Accounts, 1868 (Box-folder 01-01)
  - Accounts, 1869 (Box-folder 01-02)
  - Accounts, 1875 (Box-folder 01-03)
  - Accounts, 1871 (Box-folder 01-04)
  - Accounts, 1872 (Box-folder 01-05)
  - Accounts, 1873 (Box-folder 01-06)
  - Accounts, 1874 (Box-folder 01-07)
- Bankruptcy, 1868 - 1870
  - Bankruptcy, 1868, 1870 (Box-folder 01-08)
    Bankruptcy
- Bills, Receipts, 1842 - 1890
  - Bills, Receipts, 1842 - 1845 (Box-folder 01-09)
    Bills, Receipts
  - Bills, Receipts, 1850s, 1860s, 1870s (Box-folder 01-10)
  - Bills, Receipts, 1886 (Box-folder 01-11)
  - Bills, Receipts, 1887 (Box-folder 01-12)
  - Bills, Receipts, 1888 (Box-folder 01-13)
  - Bills, Receipts, 1889 - 1890 (Box-folder 01-14)
- Continental Life Insurance, 1869, 1875
  - Continental Life Insurance, 1869, 1875 (Box-folder 01-15)
    Continental Life Insurance
- Courts- Circuit, Commissioners, 1869 - 1886
  - Courts - Circuit, Commissioners, 1869 (Box-folder 01-16)
    Courts - Circuit, Commissioners
  - Courts - Circuit, Commissioners, 1869 (Box-folder 01-17)
  - Courts - Circuit, Commissioners, 1869 (Box-folder 01-18)
  - Courts - Circuit, Commissioners, 1870 (Box-folder 01-19)
  - Courts - Circuit, Commissioners, 1870 (Box-folder 01-20)
  - Courts - Circuit, Commissioners, 1870 (Box-folder 01-21)
  - Courts - Circuit, Commissioners, 1871 (Box-folder 01-22)
  - Courts - Circuit, Commissioners, 1872 (Box-folder 01-23)
  - Courts - Circuit, Commissioners, 1872 (Box-folder 01-24)
  - Courts - Circuit, Commissioners, 1872 (Box-folder 01-25)
  - Courts - Circuit, Commissioners, 1872 (Box-folder 01-26)
  - Courts - Circuit, Commissioners, 1873 (Box-folder 01-27)
  - Courts - Circuit, Commissioners, 1873 (Box-folder 01-28)
  - Courts - Circuit, Commissioners, 1873 (Box-folder 01-29)
  - Courts - Circuit, Commissioners, 1874 (Box-folder 01-30)
  - Courts - Circuit, Commissioners, 1874 (Box-folder 01-31)
  - Courts - Circuit, Commissioners, 1875 (Box-folder 01-32)
  - Courts - Circuit, Commissioners, 1876 (01-33)
  - Courts - Circuit, Commissioners, 1877 (01-34)
  - Courts - Circuit, Commissioners, 1877 (Box-folder 01-35)
  - Courts - Circuit, Commissioners, 1878 (Box-folder 01-36)
  - Courts - Circuit, Commissioners, 1879 (Box-folder 01-37)
  - Courts - Circuit, Commissioners, 1882 (Box-folder 01-38)
  - Courts - Circuit, Commissioners, 1884, 1886 (Box-folder 01-39)
- Courts- Common Pleas, 1870
  - Courts - Common Pleas, 1870 (Box-folder 01-40)
    Courts - Common Pleas
- Courts- District, 1860s to 1870s
  - Courts - District, 1860s, 1870s (Box-folder 01-41)
    Courts - District
- Courts- Erie County, 1868, 1879, 1881
  - Courts - Erie County, 1869, 1879, 1881 (Box-folder 01-12)
    Courts - Erie County
- Sourts- Superior Court of Buffalo, 1830s to 1869
  - Courts - Superior Court of Buffalo, 1830s, 1850s (Box-folder 01-43)
    Courts - Superior Court of Buffalo
  - Courts - Superior Court of Buffalo, 1860 - 1866 (Box-folder 01-44)
  - Courts - Superior Court of Buffalo, 1867 - 1869 (Box-folder 01-45)
- Superior of Court of Buffalo, 1872 to 1880s
  - Courts - Superior of Court of Buffalo, 1872 - 1875 (Box-folder 02-01)
    Courts - Superior of Court of Buffalo
  - Courts - Superior of Court of Buffalo, 1876 - 1879 (Box-folder 02-02)
  - Courts - Superior of Court of Buffalo, 1880s (Box-folder 02-03)
- Courts- Supreme, 1830s to 1879
  - Courts - Supreme, 1830s, 1850s (Box-folder 02-04)
    Courts - Supreme
  - Courts - Supreme, 1860-1861, 1865 (Box-folder 02-05)
  - Courts - Supreme, 1866, 1868 (Box-folder 02-06)
  - Courts - Supreme, 1869 (Box-folder 02-07)
  - Courts - Supreme, 1870, 1872 (Box-folder 02-08)
  - Courts - Supreme, 1873 - 1874 (Box-folder 02-09)
  - Courts - Supreme, 1879 (Box-folder 02-10)
- Courts- Surrogate, 1860s to 1880s
  - Courts - Surrogate, 1860s, 1870s, 1880s (Box-folder 02-11)
    Courts - Surrogate
- Estate (of Millard Powers Fillmore), 1860s to 1900s
  - Estate (of Millard Powers Fillmore), 1860s, 1870s, 1880s (Box-folder 02-12)
    Estate (of Millard Powers Fillmore)
  - Estate (of Millard Powers Fillmore), 1890 (Box-folder 02-13)
  - Estate (of Millard Powers Fillmore), 1891-1892, 1898 (Box-folder 02-14)
  - Estate (of Millard Powers Fillmore), 1900s (Box-folder 02-15)
  - Estate (of Millard Powers Fillmore), n.d. (02-16)
- Estate (settling of), 1860s to 1870s
  - Estates (settling of), 1860s, 1870s (Box-folder 02-17)
    Estates (settling of)
- Forms (unused), n.d.
  - Forms (unused), n.d. (Box-folder 02-18)
    Forms (unused)
- Miscellaneous, 1860s to 1870s
  - Miscellaneous, 1860s, 1870s (Box-folder 02-19)
    Miscellaneous
- Miscellaneous (correspondence), 1850s to 1890s
  - Miscelleaneous (correspondence), 1850s to 1890s (Box-folder 02-20)
    Miscelleaneous (correspondence)
- Sketchbook, n.d.
  - Sketchbook, n.d. (Box-folder 20( between)21)
    Sketchbook
- Miscellaneous (personal), 1830s to 1860s
  - Miscellaneous (personal), 1830s to 1860s (Box-folder 02-21)
    Miscellaneous (personal)
- Mortgages (Deeds, Bonds, Tax Searches), 1820s to 1880s
  - Mortgages (Deeds, Bonds, Tax Searches), 1820s (Box-folder 02-22)
    Mortgages (Deeds, Bonds, Tax Searches)
  - Mortgages (Deeds, Bonds, Tax Searches), 1830s (Box-folder 02-23)
  - Mortgages (Deeds, Bonds, Tax Searches), 1840s (Box-folder 02-24)
  - Mortgages (Deeds, Bonds, Tax Searches), 1854, 1856 (Box-folder 02-25)
  - Mortgages (Deeds, Bonds, Tax Searches), 1857 - 1859 (Box-folder 02-26)
  - Mortgages (Deeds, Bonds, Tax Searches), 1863-1864, 1866-1867 (Box-folder 02-27)
  - Mortgages (Deeds, Bonds, Tax Searches), 1870s (Box-folder 02-28)
  - Mortgages (Deeds, Bonds, Tax Searches), 1880s (Box-folder 02-29)
- Caroline C. Fillmore, n.d.
  Second wife of Millard Fillmore
  - Caroline C. Fillmore, n.d. (Box-folder 02-30)
    Caroline C. Fillmore (second wife of Millard Fillmore)
- Fillmore Descendents
  - Fillmore Descendents (Box-folder 02-31)
    Fillmore Descendents
- Darius Fillmore, n.d.
  Brother of Millard Fillmore. Including materials dealing with a thespian society
  - Darius Fillmore, n.d. (Box-folder 02-32)
    Darius Fillmore (brother of Millard Fillmore) Including materials dealing with a thespian society
- Fillmore Family Miscellaneous Correspondence
  - Fillmore Family Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box-folder 02-33)
    Fillmore Family Miscellaneous Correspondence
- Fillmore Family History/Genealogy, n.d.
  - Fillmore Family History / Genealogy, n.d. (Box-folder 02-34)
    Fillmore Family History / Genealogy